<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="agree">Agree</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="check_protocol_msg">To use the maintenance mode please click here agree the </string>
    <string name="check_protocol_msg_detail">Before starting the repair mode, please ensure that the data has been backed up, and the after-sales service is not responsible for possible data loss caused by the repaired product.</string>
    <string name="check_protocol_msg_sub">User Data Disclaimer</string>
    <string name="click_to_close">Click here to go to exit Maintenance Mode</string>
    <string name="close_maintenance_mode">Close maintenance Mode</string>
    <string name="create_fail">Maintenance mode creation failed, please try again later</string>
    <string name="create_fail_because_max_user">The maximum number of users in the system has been reached, please delete the avatar, double open or child mode data and try again</string>
    <string name="delete_maintenance_mode">delete maintenance mode...</string>
    <string name="disagree">Disagree</string>
    <string name="forbid_create">Maintenance mode can only be created in the main user space</string>
    <string name="maintenance_mode">Maintenance Mode</string>
    <string name="maintenance_mode_close_title">In maintenance mode</string>
    <string name="maintenance_mode_loading">Starting repair mode, phone restarting soon …</string>
    <string name="maintenance_mode_reboot">Maintenance mode reboot</string>
    <string name="maintenance_mode_title">Comprehensive protection of mobile phone data</string>
    <string name="maintenance_mode_watch_out">Protect important private data such as photos, videos, contacts, call logs, and text messages during after-sales maintenance</string>
    <string name="open">Open maintenance mode</string>
    <string name="open_maintenance_mode">Open maintenance Mode</string>
    <string name="open_maintenance_mode_msg">To avoid data loss, it is recommended that you send it in for repair after </string>
    <string name="open_maintenance_mode_msg_sub">backing up your data</string>
    <string name="reached_max_user">Reached maximum number of users</string>
    <string name="reboot_maintenance_mode">delete maintenance mode completed, for your performance of device, please reboot it</string>
    <string name="reboot_msg">Turning on the maintenance mode will automatically restart the phone, please confirm whether it is turned on immediately</string>
    <string name="reopen_maintenance_mode">It is detected that the main user of the device has been unlocked. To protect user privacy and data security, it is recommended that you re-enter the maintenance mode</string>
    <string name="set_password_main_user">Set password for main user</string>
    <string name="set_password_main_user_context">In order to ensure the security of your data, please set a lock screen password. The password cannot be retrieved, please remember it. When closing the maintenance mode, you need to verify the lock screen password you set.</string>
    <string name="setting">Setting</string>
    <string name="switch_to_maintenance_mode">Switch to maintenance Mode</string>
</resources>
