<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="AVL">AVL</string>
    <string name="Avast">Avast</string>
    <string name="DesAVL">AVL</string>
    <string name="DesAvast">Avast</string>
    <string name="DesMi">Mi</string>
    <string name="DesTencent">Tencent</string>
    <string name="Mi">Mi</string>
    <string name="Tencent">Tencent</string>
    <string name="app_name">MIUI security components</string>
    <string name="avast_dialog_cloudscan" />
    <string name="avast_dialog_dbupdate" />
    <string name="avast_dialog_header">"This feature encrypts and uploads your device's ID to Avast's servers (%s)."</string>
    <string name="avast_dialog_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="avast_dialog_title">"Avast's Privacy Policy"</string>
    <string name="avast_dialog_url">http://api.sec.miui.com/policy/proxy?p=avast&amp;l=en_US</string>
    <string name="avast_virus_type_adware_description">The virus is an adware. It automatically renders advertisements.</string>
    <string name="avast_virus_type_cryportor_description">The virus is a cryptor. It is a malicious software which is transmitted by means of replicating itself in storage space.</string>
    <string name="avast_virus_type_dropper_description">The virus is a dropper. It carries the code that installs other malicious viruses.</string>
    <string name="avast_virus_type_exploit_description">The virus is an exploit. It takes advantage of bugs or vulnerabilities in your system in order to cause unintended or unanticipated behavior.</string>
    <string name="avast_virus_type_heuristic_description">The infection is inferred by using a specific heuristic. The specific heuristic analysis says that it is a virus.</string>
    <string name="avast_virus_type_joke_description">The virus is a joke. It creates some annoying or humorous effects. It normally causes less damage than other viruses.</string>
    <string name="avast_virus_type_pup_description">"The virus is a potentially unwanted program (PUP). It's a program that may be harmful (spyware, adware, etc.), despite the fact that users give consent to download it."</string>
    <string name="avast_virus_type_rootkit_description">The virus is a rootkit. It is a type of software designed to hide the fact that an operating system has been compromised. It is used to gain control over the device by hiding deep inside the system. Rootkits allow viruses and malware to “hide in plain sight” by disguising as necessary files that normal antivirus software will overlook.</string>
    <string name="avast_virus_type_spyware_description">"The virus is a spyware. It is a software that covertly gathers user information through the user's Internet connection without his or her knowledge."</string>
    <string name="avast_virus_type_suspicious_description">A common suspicious type. The antivirus system is trying to classify it.</string>
    <string name="avast_virus_type_tool_description">The virus is a potentially evil tool similar to PUP.</string>
    <string name="avast_virus_type_trjan_description">"The virus is a trojan. It is a malware designed to provide unauthorized, remote access to a user's device. Trojans normally do not have the ability to replicate themselves like viruses. However, they can lead to other malware being installed on your device, data being stolen, or other malicious activities."</string>
    <string name="avast_virus_type_unknown_description">Unknown type of infection.</string>
    <string name="avast_virus_type_worm_description">The virus is a worm. It is a standalone malware that replicates itself in order to spread to other devices. It takes advantage of files or information transfer features of your system (e.g., networks), it can travel without any human action. Worms almost always cause at least some harm to the network.</string>
    <string name="avl_dialog_cloudscan" />
    <string name="avl_dialog_dbupdate" />
    <string name="avl_dialog_header">"This feature encrypts and uploads your device's ID to AVL's servers (%s)."</string>
    <string name="avl_dialog_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="avl_dialog_title">"AVL's Privacy Policy"</string>
    <string name="avl_dialog_url">http://api.sec.miui.com/policy/proxy?p=antiy&amp;l=en_US</string>
    <string name="com.crashlytics.android.build_id">76e0465a66214d199792867586a09063</string>
    <string name="common_ids_permission_label">Avast common ids permission</string>
    <string name="default_sdcard_volume_path" />
    <string name="default_web_client_id">484664152262-6lfq5kfidvg0o6jrnr26kf5ueijooli4.apps.googleusercontent.com</string>
    <string name="gcm_defaultSenderId">484664152262</string>
    <string name="google_api_key">AIzaSyDaFcvaCIcen1MFnR8VIUpuEnJsKpsKYJA</string>
    <string name="google_app_id">1:484664152262:android:bbb10594123b82ad1247c7</string>
    <string name="google_crash_reporting_api_key">AIzaSyDaFcvaCIcen1MFnR8VIUpuEnJsKpsKYJA</string>
    <string name="google_storage_bucket">guardprovider-c3e77.appspot.com</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="project_id">guardprovider-c3e77</string>
    <string name="tencent_dialog_cloudscan">Upload and scan app names and details using online virus definitions.</string>
    <string name="tencent_dialog_dbupdate">Update virus definitions automatically</string>
    <string name="tencent_dialog_header">"This feature encrypts and uploads your device's ID to Tencent's servers (%s)."</string>
    <string name="tencent_dialog_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="tencent_dialog_title">Tencent’s Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="tencent_dialog_url">http://api.sec.miui.com/policy/proxy?p=tencent&amp;l=en_US</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
</resources>
