<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_description">Navigate home</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_up_description">Navigate up</string>
    <string name="abc_action_menu_overflow_description">More options</string>
    <string name="abc_action_mode_done">Done</string>
    <string name="abc_activity_chooser_view_see_all">See all</string>
    <string name="abc_activitychooserview_choose_application">Choose an app</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_off">OFF</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_on">ON</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_alt_shortcut_label">Alt+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_ctrl_shortcut_label">Ctrl+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_delete_shortcut_label">delete</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_enter_shortcut_label">enter</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_function_shortcut_label">Function+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_meta_shortcut_label">Meta+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_shift_shortcut_label">Shift+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_space_shortcut_label">space</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_sym_shortcut_label">Sym+</string>
    <string name="abc_prepend_shortcut_label">Menu+</string>
    <string name="abc_search_hint">Search…</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_clear">Clear query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_query">Search query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_search">Search</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_submit">Submit query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_voice">Voice search</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with">Share with</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with_application">Share with %s</string>
    <string name="abc_toolbar_collapse_description">Collapse</string>
    <string name="accessibility_enabled">Accessibility enabled.</string>
    <string name="agree">Agree</string>
    <string name="agree_and_next">Agree</string>
    <string name="agree_terms">"I've read and agree to the User Agreement and Privacy Policy."</string>
    <string name="agree_terms_input_method_facemoji">"I've read and agreed to Facemoji Privacy Policy."</string>
    <string name="agree_terms_input_method_kika">"I've read and agreed to Kika Privacy Policy."</string>
    <string name="ai_button_desc">AI button allows you to trigger Mi AI and use Mi AI shortcuts.</string>
    <string name="ai_button_double_press">Double press</string>
    <string name="ai_button_double_press_desc">Double press AI button to complete custom tasks</string>
    <string name="ai_button_long_press">Press and hold</string>
    <string name="ai_button_long_press_desc">Press and hold AI button to talk to Mi AI</string>
    <string name="ai_button_single_press">Press</string>
    <string name="ai_button_single_press_desc">Press AI button to view Mi AI shortcuts</string>
    <string name="ai_button_title">AI button</string>
    <string name="album_introduction">Gallery allows you to manage, optimize, and edit photos and videos on your device, as well as sync them to Xiaomi Cloud.</string>
    <string name="app_name">Provision</string>
    <string name="application_package_introduction">This app allows you to install third party apps, scan them before installation, and give recommendations after it.</string>
    <string name="application_permissions">App permissions</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="backup_introduction">You can use this app to back up and restore items on your device.</string>
    <string name="boot_video_desc" />
    <string name="boot_video_replay">Play again</string>
    <string name="boot_video_skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="calculator_introduction">You can use this app for calculations, converting units and currencies, and estimating your mortgage repayments.</string>
    <string name="camera_introduction">You can use Camera to take photos and shoot videos.</string>
    <string name="carrier_introduction">"In order to provide you with better services, your device may periodically send your device version information, device identification data (including IMEI/IMSI/MSISDN/MAC address, MEID/ICCID), and approximate location information (including base station ID) to the carrier via WLAN, mobile data network, or free SMS. The carrier promises to analyze relevant information only to improve the quality of services or to provide customized services or technologies, and won't disclose relevant information to third parties in any form that identifies you personally. The specific carrier statement shall prevail. Consult your carrier regarding the cost of using this service."</string>
    <string name="clock_introduction">You can use this app to view time, as well as use timer, world clock, stopwatch, set alarms, and more.</string>
    <string name="close_location_service_setting">You can choose turn off location access in Settings > Additional settings > Privacy or restrict permissions for individual apps in Security.</string>
    <string name="cm_terms_content">"In order to improve the services provided to you, the mobile network operator of your choice may upload your personal data and the info about this device to its servers using WLAN networks or mobile data connection. This information will only be used for statistical purposes in order to improve the quality of the services and provide more personalized content. This information won't be used to identify you personally and won't be disclosed to third parties."</string>
    <string name="cm_terms_title">Mobile Network Operator Agreement</string>
    <string name="compass_introduction">You can use this app for navigation, as well as viewing coordinates, atmospheric pressure, and altitude.</string>
    <string name="congratulation_label">"You're ready to rock!​"</string>
    <string name="congratulation_swipe">Swipe up to enter the system</string>
    <string name="congratulation_title">Setup complete</string>
    <string name="content_description_complete">Complete</string>
    <string name="content_description_miui_version">MIUI 12</string>
    <string name="content_description_start">Start</string>
    <string name="content_introduction">Content Center aggregates content and services from multiple channels. Here you can read articles, watch videos, view daily featured items, and receive content recommendations.</string>
    <string name="continue_to_enable_accessibility">Keep holding down two fingers to enable accessibility.</string>
    <string name="data_traffic_enable_dialog_title">"If you aren't connected to WLAN now, your device will use mobile data. Using mobile data may generate additional carrier fees."</string>
    <string name="desc_extra_fingerprint" />
    <string name="desc_extra_international_fingerprint" />
    <string name="desc_fingerprint">Use your fingerprint to unlock your device, verify Mi Pay transactions, or to sign in to apps and services.</string>
    <string name="desc_international_fingerprint">Use your fingerprint to unlock your device, or to sign in to apps and services.</string>
    <string name="diagnose_report">Send diagnostic data to locate and analyze system issues and improve user experience. Such data may include personal information (e.g. IP, location, etc.)</string>
    <string name="disageement_abnormal_download">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this service."</string>
    <string name="disagree">Cancel</string>
    <string name="disagreement_abnormal_running">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this app. You can choose not to use this app or restrict permissions in the Settings in such cases."</string>
    <string name="disagreement_abnormal_running_fast_pairing">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions, you won't be able to use this app. You can choose to restrict permissions and turn off this feature in the Settings in such cases."</string>
    <string name="disagreement_donnot_use_application">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this app. You can choose not to use this app in such cases."</string>
    <string name="disagreement_donnot_use_product">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this product. You can choose not to use this product in such cases."</string>
    <string name="disagreement_donnot_use_service">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this service. You can choose not to use this service in such cases."</string>
    <string name="disagreement_exit_app">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this app. You can choose to sign out or restrict permissions in the Settings in such cases."</string>
    <string name="disagreement_function">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this feature. You can choose not to use this feature in such cases."</string>
    <string name="disagreement_location_service">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this service."</string>
    <string name="disagreement_terminate_service">"If you don't agree to grant such permissions or share and upload your personal information, you won't be able to use this app. You can choose to uninstall, sign out, or restrict permissions in the Settings in such cases."</string>
    <string name="download_introduction">\"Downloads\" is using Xunlei to download items on your device. This tool works for GetApps, system updates, themes, videos, and browser downloads.</string>
    <string name="enable_accessibility_canceled">Accessibility canceled.</string>
    <string name="enable_accessibility_dialog_message">You turned on TalkBack by pressing the screen with 2 fingers for more than 10 seconds. TalkBack provides voice feedback for people with visual impairments. If you turned it on by accident, tap the Cancel button, and then double tap the screen.</string>
    <string name="enable_accessibility_dialog_negative_btn">Cancel</string>
    <string name="enable_accessibility_dialog_positive_btn">OK</string>
    <string name="fast_application_introduction">Quick apps Framework allows you to create and provide services in quick apps.</string>
    <string name="fast_pairing_introduction">Mi Link allows your device to connect to Bluetooth devices nearby using MIUI Bluetooth Service. To be able to find devices nearby, allow MIUI Bluetooth Service to connect to the internet.</string>
    <string name="font_hint_large">Default text size</string>
    <string name="font_hint_normal">Increase text size</string>
    <string name="framework_introduction">Mi Services Framework allows you to use Mi Account, Mi Push, Mi Stats, and MIUI BI.</string>
    <string name="framwork_base_service">To provide you with these services, Mi Services Framework (Mi Account, Mi Push, Mi Stats, MIUI BI) needs to connect to the internet, access your location, phone number, IMEI, and IMSI, and allow your device to receive push notifications</string>
    <string name="game_introduction">Games plug-in allows you to sign in, create orders, complete payments, use coupons, and participate in promotion events.</string>
    <string name="google_service_introduction">To be able to work normally, Google Play needs to connect to the internet, access your location, be able to record audio, make calls, access calendar events, call history, sensors, storage, camera, device info, and accounts.</string>
    <string name="home_settings_miui_home">Classic</string>
    <string name="home_settings_poco_launcher">App drawer</string>
    <string name="home_settings_title">Select default launcher</string>
    <string name="ime_privacy_policy">Privacy Policy for selected keyboard</string>
    <string name="ime_privacy_policy_no_network">No network connection. View the Privacy Policy for this keyboard at %s.</string>
    <string name="input_method_category">"Choose the default keyboard that you'll use for writing messages, notes, and just about everything else. Note that you can install other third-party keyboards later."</string>
    <string name="input_method_setting">Choose keyboard</string>
    <string name="install_preinstall_app">Loading apps…</string>
    <string name="item_fingerprint">Fingerprint</string>
    <string name="item_lock_screen_password">Only screen lock</string>
    <string name="item_lock_screen_password_only">Screen lock</string>
    <string name="ktlocation_U">(KT Service Agent)</string>
    <string name="ktposition_header">Sharing location information with emergency rescue agencies</string>
    <string name="language_picker_other_languages_title">More languages</string>
    <string name="language_settings">Choose language</string>
    <string name="locale_picker_other_locale_title">More regions</string>
    <string name="locale_picker_title">Choose your region</string>
    <string name="location_U">U+ GPSnWPS</string>
    <string name="location_content">In accordance with the law, mobile carriers can obtain the location information of mobile devices to comply with the requirements of emergency rescue agencies (fire departments and the police) which pursue security and emergency rescue purposes.</string>
    <string name="location_introduction">Location-based services find products and services near you.</string>
    <string name="location_location">Emergency rescue agencies can obtain your current location upon request</string>
    <string name="lockscreen_introduction">Wallpaper Carousel allows you to get fresh images delivered to your Lock screen daily.</string>
    <string name="mint_keyboard_oobe_checkbox">"I've read and agreed to Mint Keyboard Privacy Policy"</string>
    <string name="mint_keyboard_oobe_terms">Mint Keyboard Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="miui_privacy_policy_no_network">"You don't have an internet connection. View the Privacy Policy at %s."</string>
    <string name="miui_terms_no_network">"You don't have an internet connection. View the User Agreement at %s."</string>
    <string name="mobile_network">Using mobile data</string>
    <string name="move_data_dialog_box_le">"This allows using mobile data and GPS connection based on the user's request. Syncing accounts and other items may require using mobile data depending on the smartphone specifications."</string>
    <string name="move_data_dialog_box_title">Unless you have a plan with unlimited data, using mobile data may generate additional carrier fees. Use mobile data anyway?</string>
    <string name="move_data_dialog_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="move_data_dialog_title">You can restrict mobile data connection in the Settings later</string>
    <string name="move_data_dialog_use">Use</string>
    <string name="msim_setting_default_data">Data SIM</string>
    <string name="msim_setting_default_voice">Default SIM for calls</string>
    <string name="multisim_settings_category">SIM card settings</string>
    <string name="multisim_settings_title">2 SIM cards detected</string>
    <string name="navigation_picker_gesture_guide">Gesture guide</string>
    <string name="navigation_picker_radio_text_full_screen">Full screen gestures</string>
    <string name="navigation_picker_radio_text_virtual_key">Buttons</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="next_fingerprint">Next</string>
    <string name="note_introduction">This app allows you to create, view, and edit notes.</string>
    <string name="other_settings">Additional settings</string>
    <string name="other_settings_ad_dialog_agree">Turn on</string>
    <string name="other_settings_ad_dialog_content">"When personalized ad recommendations are off, you'll still see the same quantity of ads as when the feature is on. The ads, however, will no longer be relevant as they won't be based on your personal preferences."</string>
    <string name="other_settings_ad_dialog_disagree">Turn off</string>
    <string name="other_settings_ad_disable_summary">Turn on to personalize ads</string>
    <string name="other_settings_ad_enable">Personalized ads</string>
    <string name="other_settings_ad_enable_summary">Personalize ads based on your interests</string>
    <string name="other_settings_auto_update">Automatic system updates</string>
    <string name="other_settings_auto_update_summary">MIUI will select the best time to download and install updates. Your device will be rebooted automatically to apply changes.</string>
    <string name="other_settings_enhanced_lockscreen">Wallpaper Carousel</string>
    <string name="other_settings_enhanced_lockscreen_for_india">Glance for Mi</string>
    <string name="other_settings_enhanced_lockscreen_privacy_index">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="other_settings_enhanced_lockscreen_summary">Get curated images and stories delivered to your Lock screen daily. %1$s and %2$s</string>
    <string name="other_settings_enhanced_lockscreen_summary_index">End User Licence Agreement</string>
    <string name="other_settings_location">Location</string>
    <string name="other_settings_location_summary">Allow apps to access your location</string>
    <string name="other_settings_upload_debug_log_summary">Usage stats which help us locate and solve issues may contain your personal info</string>
    <string name="other_settings_upload_debug_log_title">Send diagnostic data automatically</string>
    <string name="other_settings_user_experience">User Experience Program</string>
    <string name="other_settings_user_experience_summary">Help us improve our products and services by sharing your usage stats with us. View details</string>
    <string name="other_settings_user_experience_summary_index">View details</string>
    <string name="permission_account">Access accounts on your device:</string>
    <string name="permission_account_introduction">For signing in with Mi Account</string>
    <string name="permission_application_package_introduction">For accessing storage in order to parse and scan installation packages</string>
    <string name="permission_backup">Accessing storage</string>
    <string name="permission_backup_introduction">For accessing and saving backups on your device</string>
    <string name="permission_call_records">Access call history:</string>
    <string name="permission_call_records_introduction">For accessing call history in order to display blocked items</string>
    <string name="permission_call_state_introduction">For accessing phone status, recording calls, and pausing recordings during incoming calls</string>
    <string name="permission_clock_info_introduction">For saving alarm data</string>
    <string name="permission_contact">Access contacts:</string>
    <string name="permission_contact_introduction">For providing Blocklist functionality and calling emergency contacts</string>
    <string name="permission_different_device_introduction">For identifying services associated with different devices</string>
    <string name="permission_different_info_introduction">For identifying different devices</string>
    <string name="permission_direct_call">Make calls:</string>
    <string name="permission_direct_call_introduction">For adding items to Blocklist</string>
    <string name="permission_download_introduction">For caching downloaded items and saving them on your device</string>
    <string name="permission_imei_service">For accessing IMEI to provide services associated with your device</string>
    <string name="permission_interaction_introduction">For saving photos and videos on device</string>
    <string name="permission_location">Access location info:</string>
    <string name="permission_location_introduction">For providing location-based services</string>
    <string name="permission_log_introduction">For saving logs</string>
    <string name="permission_login_introduction">For signing in and managing system accounts</string>
    <string name="permission_message_introduction">For sending messages to blocked contacts</string>
    <string name="permission_phone_imei_device">For accessing IMEI in order to identify devices</string>
    <string name="permission_phone_network">For accessing network type in order to optimize and adjust downloadable items</string>
    <string name="permission_phone_service">Access phone number, IMEI, and IMSI:</string>
    <string name="permission_photo_introduction">For saving images to Gallery and publishing statuses</string>
    <string name="permission_photo_video">Take photos and record video:</string>
    <string name="permission_photo_video_introduction">For taking photos, recording videos, and using flash</string>
    <string name="permission_picture_introduction">For saving, editing, and syncing photos and videos</string>
    <string name="permission_read_call_records">Edit call history:</string>
    <string name="permission_read_call_records_introduction">For adding items to call history and deleting blocked calls</string>
    <string name="permission_read_note_introduction">For accessing notes and attachments</string>
    <string name="permission_read_write_file">Access and save files and photos on your device:</string>
    <string name="permission_read_write_file_introduction">For accessing, saving, and caching items on your device</string>
    <string name="permission_recorder_file_introduction">For accessing and saving audio recordings</string>
    <string name="permission_recording">Record calls and audio:</string>
    <string name="permission_recording_introduction">For recording audio while recording video</string>
    <string name="permission_screen_shoot_introduction">For accessing and saving screen recordings</string>
    <string name="permission_send_message">Send SMS</string>
    <string name="permission_user_record_introduction">For recording audio</string>
    <string name="permission_virusscan_introduction">For performing virus scan and optimizing your device</string>
    <string name="permission_xunlei_introduction">For signing in and managing system accounts in order to provide Xunlei services</string>
    <string name="poco_agree_terms_other">(Including POCO Launcher Privacy Policy and User Agreement)</string>
    <string name="poco_launcher_privacy_policy">POCO Launcher Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="poco_launcher_user_agreement">POCO Launcher User Agreement</string>
    <string name="position_header">Sharing location information</string>
    <string name="position_subheading">Location info</string>
    <string name="pref_title_data_slot">Preferred data SIM card</string>
    <string name="pref_title_voice_slot">Preferred voice SIM card</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="protect_persoanl_info_statement">We shall protect your personal information in accordance with the relevant laws, regulations, and privacy policies.</string>
    <string name="provision_back">Back</string>
    <string name="provision_inputmethod_policy_description">"
View the selected keyboard's Privacy Policy."</string>
    <string name="provision_inputmethod_policy_description1">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="provision_next">Next</string>
    <string name="provision_skip_underline">Skip</string>
    <string name="recorder_introduction">You can use this app to record audio and back up recordings to the cloud.</string>
    <string name="require_authority_statement">To allow us to provide you with basic services, you need to grant the following permissions in order for us to collect your personal information:</string>
    <string name="require_network_authority_statement">To allow us to provide you with basic services, you need to connect to the internet and grant the following permissions in order for us to collect your personal information:</string>
    <string name="screen_recording_introduction">"This app allows you to record what's happening on your screen."</string>
    <string name="search_menu_title">Search</string>
    <string name="security_introduction">You can use this app to clear trash on your device, find and neutralize viruses, optimize performance for gaming, save battery, manage apps, permissions, and more.</string>
    <string name="security_mobile_account_introduction">For signing in and managing system accounts</string>
    <string name="service_agreement">"I've read and agreed to the terms and conditions."</string>
    <string name="service_name_album">Gallery</string>
    <string name="service_name_application_package">Package installer</string>
    <string name="service_name_backup">Backups</string>
    <string name="service_name_calculator">Calculator</string>
    <string name="service_name_camera">Camera</string>
    <string name="service_name_carrier">Statement on carrier services</string>
    <string name="service_name_clock">Clock</string>
    <string name="service_name_compass">Compass</string>
    <string name="service_name_content_center">Content Center</string>
    <string name="service_name_download">Downloads</string>
    <string name="service_name_fast_application">Quick apps Framework</string>
    <string name="service_name_fast_pairing">Mi Link</string>
    <string name="service_name_game">Games plug-in</string>
    <string name="service_name_google_service">Statement on Google services</string>
    <string name="service_name_location">Location-based services</string>
    <string name="service_name_lockscreen">Wallpaper Carousel</string>
    <string name="service_name_note">Notes</string>
    <string name="service_name_recorder">Recorder</string>
    <string name="service_name_screen_recording">Screen Recorder</string>
    <string name="service_name_security">Security</string>
    <string name="service_name_service_framework">Mi Services Framework</string>
    <string name="service_policy"><Data>Read and agree to our &lt;a href=%1$s>Privacy Policy&lt;/a >.</Data></string>
    <string name="service_policy_download"><Data>Before using our services, read and agree to &lt;a href=%1$s>Xunlei Privacy Policy&lt;/a >.</Data></string>
    <string name="service_privacy_index">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="service_security_over_r"><Data>Read and agree to our &lt;a href=%1$s>Privacy Policy&lt;/a > before using Security.&lt;br/>&lt;br/>In accordance with Android 11 standards, a one-time permission will be withdrawn within 5 seconds after the corresponding app stops running. If you open the app during this short period of time, the permission will be withdrawn then.</Data></string>
    <string name="servicestate_title">Statement on basic services</string>
    <string name="setting_locale">Setting region…</string>
    <string name="shut_down">Shut down</string>
    <string name="sim_card_detecting">Checking for SIM card…</string>
    <string name="sim_card_detecting_check">"Couldn't find SIM card. Make sure SIM card is properly installed and you have sufficient funds on your balance."</string>
    <string name="sim_card_detecting_confirm_turn_on_network">Allow connecting to mobile data networks? If you do, the SIM card you insert will be used to connect to mobile data networks.</string>
    <string name="sim_card_detecting_title">Checking for SIM card…</string>
    <string name="sim_card_detection">Insert SIM card</string>
    <string name="sim_card_detection_info">To insert your SIM card, read the instructions that came with your device.</string>
    <string name="sim_card_detection_mobile_not_available">"SIM card couldn't connect to the network"</string>
    <string name="sim_dectection_next">Continue</string>
    <string name="sim_redetection">Check again</string>
    <string name="sim_scard_detecting_check_mobile_not_available">"Your SIM card couldn't connect to a valid carrier network. Make sure you have sufficient funds on your balance and try to connect again."</string>
    <string name="skip_gesture_guide_dialog_message">Make sure you know how to use full screen gestures before selecting this option.</string>
    <string name="skip_gesture_guide_dialog_negative_btn">Cancel</string>
    <string name="skip_gesture_guide_dialog_positive_btn">OK</string>
    <string name="skip_gesture_guide_dialog_title">Full screen gestures</string>
    <string name="skip_underline">Skip this step</string>
    <string name="start_up_slogan">Yours alone</string>
    <string name="status_bar_notification_info_overflow">999+</string>
    <string name="suggested_actions_uri">android.resource://com.android.provision/raw/suggested_actions</string>
    <string name="summary_not_set">Not set</string>
    <string name="system_navigation_mode">System navigation mode</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use">Terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_ble_htmlViewer">, Fused Location Provider, HTML Viewer</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_label">"Read our User Agreement and Privacy Policy to understand what information we collect, how we use it, and what choices are available to you.
You must agree to our User Agreement and Privacy Policy before you can use MIUI.
%s and Mi Account components will connect to the internet and acquire your location."</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_label_Mistore">, Mi Store system plug-in</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_label_mab">, MAB</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_label_package">, Package installer</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_label_phrase">, Frequent phrases</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_label_systemhelper">, Self-registered service</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_label_updater">, Updater</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_lable_apps">Mi services, Mi SIM activation services, Xiaomi Cloud, Find device, Home screen, Games, MIUI Daemon, MSA system components, translation services, MIUI SDK, Quick apps, App vault, statistics, Mi Link</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_lable_default_input_method_facemoji">"

You must agree to Facemoji Privacy Policy before using this feature."</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_lable_default_input_method_kika">"

You must agree to Kika Privacy Policy before using this feature."</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_lable_default_input_method_mint">"

You must agree to Mint Keyboard Privacy Policy before using this feature."</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_lable_gms">, Google Play services</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_lable_smart_cards">, Smart cards</string>
    <string name="terms_of_use_lable_vsimcore">, MConnService</string>
    <string name="terms_privacy_policy_input_method_facemoji">Facemoji Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="terms_privacy_policy_input_method_kika">Kika Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="title_fingerprint">Set password</string>
    <string name="user_agreement">User Agreement</string>
    <string name="user_agreement_declare">Before using MIUI, you must read and agree to our User Agreement and Privacy Policy. While your device is being activated, Mi SIM Activation Service, Xiaomi Cloud, Find device, Home screen, Frequent phrases, Translation Service, MIUI Daemon, HTML Viewer, MIUI SDK, AI Assistant, Battery and performance, Power Detector, Joyose, OS AI Setting, Permissions Manager, and Updater will connect to the network. Smart services will connect to the network and access your location.</string>
    <string name="voice_assist_advice">Mi AI allows you to use voice controls, but it consumes more power (+1% every hour).</string>
    <string name="voice_assist_condition">"You'll be able to use Mi AI in these cases:r
1. When the screen is on.r
2. When you're listening to music with your screen off."</string>
    <string name="voice_assist_desp">Say \"Mi AI\" into your phone. Mi AI will recognize your voice and will be able to control your device.</string>
    <string name="voice_assist_title">Wake with voice</string>
    <string name="welcome">Welcome</string>
    <string name="wizard_script_uri">android.resource://com.android.provision/raw/wizard_script</string>
    <string name="zone_picker_title">Choose time zone</string>
</resources>
