<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="console_guide_subtitle_small_window">"Minimize the window that's being cast to be able to use other features of your mobile device"</string>
    <string name="dialog_scanning_precondition">Turn on Wi-Fi and Bluetooth on your mobile device to use Casting.</string>
    <string name="global_privacy_main">"Projecting the items from your mobile device's screen on a bigger external monitor."</string>
    <string name="help_page_text_03">"Casting is projecting the items from your mobile device's screen on a bigger external monitor. It allows you to share images and videos with your friends and family without using mobile data."</string>
    <string name="help_page_text_09">"Tap the \"Cast\" toggle on your device's Notification shade. Turn on both WLAN and Bluetooth for a more stable connection."</string>
    <string name="help_page_text_17">"You can project items from your Xiaomi device on most Mi TV models with Bluetooth capabilities without turning on Miracast manually.
If you need to turn on Miracast, press the [MENU] button and select My apps > Casting > Miracast."</string>
    <string name="privacy_explain">"Welcome to Casting! Casting allows projecting the items from your mobile device's screen on a bigger external monitor. This app needs to connect to the internet and requires the following permissions to be able to work normally:"</string>
    <string name="privacy_text_1"><Data>"Welcome to Casting! Casting allows projecting the items from your mobile device's screen on a bigger external monitor.
We shall protect your personal information in accordance with the relevant laws, regulations, and privacy policies. Some features are provided by a third party service provider HappyCast. Before using this feature, read and agree to &lt;a href=%2$s>HappyCast Legal Statement&lt;/a> and &lt;a href=%1$s>HappyCast Privacy Policy&lt;/a>.
To be able to work normally, this app needs to connect to the internet and requires the following permissions in order to collect your personal information:"</Data></string>
    <string name="privacy_text_pemission">"• Access and save images on your device
For projecting these items on external monitors
• Record calls and audio
For casting audio on external devices
• Access phone number, IMEI, and IMSI
For identifying your device
• Access your location 
For finding devices nearby"</string>
    <string name="san_wait_msg_3">"External devices are easier to find when they're connected to the same network as your mobile device"</string>
    <string name="screen_projection_characteristics_small_window_summary">"Minimize the window that's being cast to be able to use other features of your mobile device."</string>
    <string name="screen_projection_example_document_summary">Display presentations on an external monitor while using your mobile device to switch between slides and view notes. Go to File Manager > Docs to try this feature.</string>
    <string name="toast_msg_for_small_window">"You can minimize the window that's being cast to be able to use other features of your mobile device without interrupting the casting process."</string>
    <string name="toast_nfc_dont_move">"Don't move your mobile device away"</string>
</resources>
