<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="volte_switch_title">VoLTE Calls</string>
    <string name="wifi_call_accept">I Accept</string>
    <string name="wifi_call_available_message">"WLAN Calling is a service of your mobile operator, Orange Polska S.A.
Please read the description of the service provided by your operator:

WLAN Calling service enables you to make and receive voice calls over any WLAN internet connection, even in a situation where you are outside any mobile network’s coverage. Once the service is active for your mobile number, every time you connect to a WLAN network, your voice calls will be performed using WLAN Calling. This will be presented to you by a dedicated icon on the notification bar.

In the case your WLAN connection is of poor quality or your device is outside a WLAN network’s coverage, your phone will make calls using an available mobile network.

Your calls made with WLAN Calling in Poland are charged in the same way as your regular mobile calls in your mobile tariff plan. Incoming calls in Poland are free of charge. If you make WLAN Calling calls outside Poland your calls may be charged with a dedicated price specified in your mobile tariff plan’s price list.

Notwithstanding, your WLAN connections may be charged independently by the provider of your WLAN connection.

Once you press the ACCEPT button and your phone connects to a WLAN network, your WLAN Calling service will be activated. You can disable the WLAN Calling at any time using the phone menu.

Detailed description of your WLAN Calling service could be found at www.orange.pl/wificalling

Please note that in order to enable routing of your emergency calls (eg. such as 112 calls) to the closest emergency centre , suitable for your actual location, your emergency calls in the WLAN Calling services will be carried by your device through any mobile network available at a given moment Only in the cases where no mobile network is available an emergency call will be routed via WLAN Calling service. Unfortunately, in such cases we will not know your precise location and therefore your emergency call may be routed to the not to the closest Emergency centre, regarding your actual location.

In regard to your use of WLAN Calling we (ie. Orange Polska SA, acting as your personal data controller) will process your data on the number and model of the device, on which you use WLAN Calling, the software used on the device, the endpoint of the network used to connect with WLAN Calling (including the IP address and the country, to which this IP address is attributed), and the time and duration of each call, in order to perform and settle the service, answer the complaints, and to perform statutory obligation. We will process these data for the duration of the agreement on providing telecommunication services between you and us, and after its termination - for the period of recovery of claims and of performing other tasks defined in the provisions of law. Providing the data is voluntary, but it is necessary to use the service. You have the right to access and to rectify your data.

Please find our data: Orange Polska S.A., address: Aleje Jerozolimskie 160, 02-326 Warsaw, Poland, registered in the Register of the Enterpreneurs of District Court for the Capital City of Warsaw in Warsaw, XII Commercial Division of the National Court Register (KRS), under entry number 0000010681, NIP (tax ID) 526-02-50-995; with share capital (fully paid up) of PLN 3,937,072,437.00."</string>
    <string name="wifi_call_cancel">More info</string>
    <string name="wifi_call_help_message_1">WLAN Calling is the service providing the ability to make and receive voice calls over the Internet connection in any available WLAN network, even if you are out of mobile coverage. The WLAN Calling icon on the notification bar (shown below) indicates that all your calls are using WLAN Calling.</string>
    <string name="wifi_call_help_message_2">"In a case the WLAN connection is getting weak or you get out of the WLAN coverage your mobile phone would switch to mobile network.

Using WLAN Calling is rated according to the service rates provided by your mobile operator. Details on www.orange.pl/wificalling

Please note that calls to Emergency Numbers eg. 112 will be routed through a mobile network. In case there is no mobile coverage the Emergency Calls could be routed via WLAN Calling service. In such cases your mobile operator may not be able to determine your exact location information and therefore would route your call to the Emergency Centre which is not the closest one for your actual location."</string>
    <string name="wifi_call_help_title">WLAN Calling - Help</string>
    <string name="wifi_call_notification_message">"WLAN Calling is the service providing the ability to make and receive voice calls over the Internet connection in any available WLAN network, even if you are out of mobile coverage. The WLAN Calling icon on the notification bar indicate that all your calls are using WLAN Calling.

Details on www.orange.pl/wificalling

Choose the SETTINGS menu below to activate your WLAN Calling service on your mobile device."</string>
    <string name="wifi_call_setting">WLAN Calling</string>
    <string name="wifi_call_welcome_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="wificall_switch_title">WLAN Calling</string>
</resources>
